Joriel Fairbanks

Santa Fe, NM 87507 discordaccoun34@gmail.com

+15053038068

I have spent countless hours working in computers and can sell you just about anything computer-related. I work well with others and have somewhat of an extroverted personality. I work well with kids and animals and have no allergies. I strive to be a computer nerd and help assist with both backend management and frontend overseeing to help provide users with a positive experience.

Work Experience

Intern

National Center for Genome Resources-Santa Fe, NM June 2024 to August 2024

- Helped Setup a Server System
- · Worked on Backend Database Management
- Assisted with Company Management
- Created A Backend Database

Cat Sitter

Santa Fe, NM

June 2022 to August 2022

Basic cat sitting gig. Made sure cat was happy and healthy during the whole process. Made sure that the cat was in a positive mood.

Education

Middle school education

Santa Fe Prepatory school - Santa Fe, NM

August 2019 to Present

Skills

- Math
- IT
- · Technical support
- Leadership
- · Heavy lifting
- Babysitting
- Computer skills (7 years)
- · Pet sitting
- Back-end development (2 years)

- Backend Management (2 years)
- Tutoring

Languages

- Spanish Intermediate
- English Fluent

Certifications and Licenses

Driver's License

June 2024 to Present

Standard DL